<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hospitality on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/hospitality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hospitality on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2020, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 16:53:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/hospitality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>French restaurant delights with live LouderVoice customer reviews on iPad</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/11/06/french-restaurant-delights-with-live-loudervoice-customer-reviews-on-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/11/06/french-restaurant-delights-with-live-loudervoice-customer-reviews-on-ipad/</guid>
      <description>We always strongly encourage our clients to request reviews using every channel available to them, particularly if the bulk of their business is not online. This can be done using receipts, invoices, compliment slips, phone calls or, in the case of our latest restaurant client in France, using an iPad!
This is simply a superb idea by l&amp;#8217;Auberge des Trois Pucelles near Grenoble and our partners Thierry André FOUCHER and WSI Belledonne Digital Strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The hospitality industry is embracing customer reviews with LouderVoice</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/06/28/the-hospitality-industry-is-embracing-customer-reviews-with-loudervoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 17:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/06/28/the-hospitality-industry-is-embracing-customer-reviews-with-loudervoice/</guid>
      <description>We were very interested to see an MSNBC article on how hotels are embracing online customer reviews. It matches our own experience, as our reviewing solutions are proving a major hit with businesses in the hospitality and travel sectors everywhere. We have seen a string of deployments in UK, Ireland, France and the US in recent months.
As part of this growth, we&amp;#8217;re delighted to announce that we have have just gone live with the Dalata Group&amp;#8217;s 11 Maldron and 14 partner hotels in Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Website Marketing Event</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/25/hotel-website-marketing-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 13:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/25/hotel-website-marketing-event/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I attended the excellent Hotel Website Marketing event in Dublin organised by Proactiv Marketing. It was a real highlight of 2009 for me with fantastic speaker after fantastic speaker. I walked away with a ton of to-dos for LouderVoice.
I spoke on the benefit of on-site customer reviews for hotels. The core message was that you can grow on-site sales, reduce online ad spend and improve your customer service by adding reviews to your site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>