<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Le Web on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/le-web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Le Web on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2017, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 09:58:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/le-web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice in Ireland Demozone at Le Web</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2010/12/02/loudervoice-in-ireland-demozone-at-le-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 09:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2010/12/02/loudervoice-in-ireland-demozone-at-le-web/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s that time of the year again! LouderVoice has been at Le Web every year since 2006. Back then, it was just some ideas and a very basic Alpha, this time we are part of the Irish Pavilion.
 Enterprise Ireland has put together a unique Demozone at Le Web. 11 hot Irish start-ups including LouderVoice will be there. A single place where we can meet, have a coffee and show you what we do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Klipsch USA Pumps Up The Volume with LouderVoice</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/12/21/klipsch-usa-pumps-up-the-volume-with-loudervoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2009 11:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/12/21/klipsch-usa-pumps-up-the-volume-with-loudervoice/</guid>
      <description>We really are jumping up and down with excitement to finally announce that LouderVoice&amp;#8217;s first US client went live just before Le Web recently. Klipsch USA now has the LouderVoice customer review system across the entire klipsch.com web-site.
 For those in Europe not familiar with this legendary US brand, it had defined high-end audio since 1946 and is adored by audiophiles everywhere.
 Building on over 60 years of experience in hifi equipment, they also have the absolute best headphones and docks anywhere for iPhones, iPods and other MP3 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice at Le Web</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/12/07/loudervoice-at-le-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/12/07/loudervoice-at-le-web/</guid>
      <description>Conor will be at Le Web in Paris from tomorrow afternoon until Friday morning. If you&amp;#8217;d like to meet up to discuss any aspect of the LouderVoice business then feel free to contact him via any of the following methods:
 Mobile: +353-87-9790297 Twitter: @conoro e-mail: conor AT loudervoice DOT com  Hope to see you there, it&amp;#8217;s building up to be the best Le Web ever!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>