<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rich Snippets on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/rich-snippets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rich Snippets on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2017, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 11:48:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/rich-snippets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice SEO Add-On Now Available for Expression Engine</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2012/08/22/loudervoice-seo-add-on-now-available-for-expression-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 11:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2012/08/22/loudervoice-seo-add-on-now-available-for-expression-engine/</guid>
      <description>Many of our clients on PHP platforms like WordPress, Joomla, Drupal have long benefited from our SEO Add-On.
All of our Packages provide Google Juice and Star Ratings in Search results to client sites via our review Hub, LouderYou. The advantage of this approach is ease of deployment. Our code can be added in seconds to a web-page and reviews are then live. Those reviews are indexed on our hub within hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews SEO Add-On for ASP.NET just released</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2012/05/10/loudervoice-reviews-seo-add-on-for-asp-net-just-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 18:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2012/05/10/loudervoice-reviews-seo-add-on-for-asp-net-just-released/</guid>
      <description>One of the most common requests we get from partners and customers is to have the same reviews SEO functionality on ASP.NET as they do for PHP and WordPress sites. And we&amp;#8217;re delighted to say that this is now available.
All of our Packages provide Google Juice and Star Ratings in Search results to client sites via our review Hub, LouderYou. The advantage of this approach is ease of deployment. Our code can be added in seconds to a web-page and reviews are then live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews Plugin for WordPress now available</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2012/03/02/loudervoice-reviews-plugin-for-wordpress-now-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 16:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2012/03/02/loudervoice-reviews-plugin-for-wordpress-now-available/</guid>
      <description>More and more sites are moving to WordPress as their platform. We have long been WP users and all of our sites are built on it.
The LouderVoice reviews system has always supported WordPress sites but we recently decided to make it even easier to deploy on them.
 The new LouderVoice Reviews plug-in is now available and included in the price of all of our Packages. With a few quick clicks, you can install the plug-in and configure reviews for one or more pages on any WP site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastnet Line Cork-Swansea Ferry on-board with LouderVoice</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2010/08/06/fastnet-line-cork-swansea-ferry-on-board-with-loudervoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 14:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2010/08/06/fastnet-line-cork-swansea-ferry-on-board-with-loudervoice/</guid>
      <description>Business books will be written about the amazing story of the new Fastnet Line Ferry to Ireland. This much needed service operating from Swansea to Cork is proving to be a major success for the region. So you can imagine our excitement at LouderVoice becoming part of this story by powering the customer reviews on their site.
 Whilst reviews are important for any business, their importance to new businesses cannot be under-estimated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>