<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Widget on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/widget/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Widget on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:01:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/widget/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews on Facebook Pages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2010/08/27/loudervoice-reviews-on-facebook-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2010/08/27/loudervoice-reviews-on-facebook-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have just added a new Facebook capability for all of our customers. They can now show all their latest reviews in a dedicated “Our Reviews” tab on &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.facebook.com/LouderVoice?v=app_140294209327173&amp;amp;ref=ts#!/LouderVoice?v=wall&amp;amp;ref=ts&#34;&gt;their Facebook Page&lt;/a&gt;. Whilst our Facebook Connect implementation has always given reviewers the ability to post their reviews to their personal wall, this new feature enables our clients to showcase their reviews from all their products and services in one place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now a simple review written on a client’s site or submitted by SMS can appear on their Facebook Page within minutes, building confidence and guiding others who want to know more about that business. Fundamentally it’s about selling by word of mouth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Wins a Golden Spider</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2009/11/22/loudervoice-wins-a-golden-spider/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 19:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2009/11/22/loudervoice-wins-a-golden-spider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We were terribly disappointed last Thursday that massive flooding in West Cork prevented us from attending the 2009 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.goldenspiders.ie/&#34;&gt;Golden Spiders Awards&lt;/a&gt;. The awards are the most high profile in Ireland and a win can have serious business benefits locally.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So imagine our shock to hear that &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.goldenspiders.ie/winners_2009.php&#34;&gt;we won the e-business category&lt;/a&gt;! We were up against some incredibly impressive competition. Getting this recognition from our industry peers on the judging panel really is satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews on Fitzgerald Group Hotels</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2009/10/12/loudervoice-reviews-on-fitzgerald-group-hotels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 08:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2009/10/12/loudervoice-reviews-on-fitzgerald-group-hotels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve spent the past few months in &lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/business&#34;&gt;LouderVoice&lt;/a&gt; creating Version 2 of our review widget and have been quietly rolling it out on sites since early August. In our humble opinion, it is the best widget-based reviews solution on the market globally. Not only can it be implemented on most sites in under 10 minutes, it is also fully Facebook and Twitter enabled and can be easily styled to blend seamlessly into your site&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Brothers goes live with the new LouderVoice Reviews Widget</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2009/04/28/bubble-brothers-goes-live-with-the-new-loudervoice-reviews-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2009/04/28/bubble-brothers-goes-live-with-the-new-loudervoice-reviews-widget/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re pleased as punch to announce that our brand new customer reviews widget has just gone live on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bubblebrothers.com/proddetail.php?prod=HIGH01&#34;&gt;Bubble Brothers&lt;/a&gt; wine site. Julian, their &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bubblebrothers.com/blog/&#34;&gt;Wine 2.0 guru&lt;/a&gt;, has always been at the forefront of social media adoption and the addition of our widget complements all of their other online activities beautifully.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bubblebrothers.com/proddetail.php?prod=HIGH01&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter size-medium wp-image-211&#34; title=&#34;highfield_bubblebrothers&#34; src=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/highfield_bubblebrothers-300x297.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;highfield_bubblebrothers&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;297&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The key thing about the widget is the ease of implementation. One line of code was added to the Bubble Brothers product page template (they use &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ecommercetemplates.com/&#34;&gt;Ecommerce Templates&lt;/a&gt; for their site), a few minor logo tweaks later and they were up and running. No development on their side and just some quick colour/size adjustments by us. That’s all it takes to review-enable an entire site!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
