<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oem on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/oem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oem on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2017, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 14:55:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/oem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice in 2008</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/01/04/loudervoice-in-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/01/04/loudervoice-in-2008/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;ve had a fantastic year in LouderVoice and it looks like 2009 is going to be even better with a raft of new releases in the next few months. Looking back over last year we achieved the following:
 In January we launched Flag Tag reviewing which enabled any blogger to have their blog reviews collected by LouderVoice with two simple tags on a post. We also added Twitter/SMS/Jaiku hashtag support In February we sponsored the Best Blog Post in the Irish Blog Awards In March we did our first major revamp with LouderVoice V2 adding on-site reviews and a ton of other features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Klipsch.co.uk goes live</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2008/11/12/klipschcouk-goes-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 11:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2008/11/12/klipschcouk-goes-live/</guid>
      <description>We are incredibly happy to announce that Klipsch has just launched its UK specific site. Not only are they selling amazing audio equipment but the reviews there are powered by LouderVoice.
When you are investing £1000 in a sub-woofer, you want to be sure you are picking the right one. Reviews by other customers can help you make that decision. The Klipsch guys understand that those reviews are a win-win for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>