<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Reviews on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://loudervoice.com/tags/social-reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Reviews on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 15:28:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://loudervoice.com/tags/social-reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice and WSI team-up to Power Social Media and Social Reviews for UK SMEs</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/06/25/loudervoice-and-wsi-team-up-to-power-social-media-and-social-reviews-for-uk-smes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 15:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/06/25/loudervoice-and-wsi-team-up-to-power-social-media-and-social-reviews-for-uk-smes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LouderVoice and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.totalwsinetsolutions.com/&#34;&gt;WSI&lt;/a&gt; have been working together globally since early 2011. We have now joined forces to offer a compelling Social solution for SMEs in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Online marketing is an ever-moving target and it can be hard for SMEs to feel on top of everything. To solve this, WSI’s offerings and &lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/products&#34;&gt;LouderVoice’s Social Reviews&lt;/a&gt; are now available as an off-the-shelf solution that is optimised for the UK. Every business can have their online presence live and social-powered with almost no effort.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Word of Mouth Still Most Trusted Resource Says Nielsen</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/04/16/word-of-mouth-still-most-trusted-resource-says-nielsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 09:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/04/16/word-of-mouth-still-most-trusted-resource-says-nielsen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nielsen’s latest Global Trust in Advertising report, which surveyed more than 28,000 Internet respondents in 56 countries, shows that 92% of people trust recommendations from friends and family, followed closely by 70% trusting online reviews.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are the highlight stats. Read the great piece about it over on &lt;a href=&#34;http://socialcommercetoday.com/word-of-mouth-still-most-trusted-resource-says-nielsen-implications-for-social-commerce/&#34;&gt;Social Commerce Today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/trust-in-advertising.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-full wp-image-2605 aligncenter&#34; title=&#34;trust-in-advertising&#34; src=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/trust-in-advertising.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;570&#34; height=&#34;486&#34; srcset=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/trust-in-advertising.png 570w, https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/trust-in-advertising-300x255.png 300w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 570px) 100vw, 570px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve been in the reviews business for quite a few years so we’re not remotely surprised by this data. But our experience over the past 12 months is that small businesses are now realising the importance of reviews and adding customer reviews solutions to their sites and Facebook. This is as true in rural Ireland as it is in Del Mar California.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Launches Dedicated Social Reviews for Facebook</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/03/06/loudervoice-launches-dedicated-social-reviews-for-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 12:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/03/06/loudervoice-launches-dedicated-social-reviews-for-facebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As the first company to do Social Reviews on Twitter, way back in 2007, we have finally given in to all the (many!) demands for a Facebook-only solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of our Packages have had a powerful Facebook component since 2009 but &lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/products/facebook-reviews-package/&#34;&gt;this Package&lt;/a&gt; enables small businesses, who may not even have their own web-site, to show and solicit customer reviews on their Facebook Page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many of the businesses who have contacted us had previously used the old built-in Facebook reviews App. Whilst it was pretty awful, it worked, and they miss it! So we love being the company to put a smile back on their faces.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
