<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E Commerce on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://loudervoice.com/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E Commerce on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2024, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 16:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://loudervoice.com/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking at IIA’s “8 More Ways to Sell Even More Stuff”</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2011/02/23/speaking-at-iias-8-more-ways-to-sell-even-more-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 16:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2011/02/23/speaking-at-iias-8-more-ways-to-sell-even-more-stuff/</guid>
      <description>The IIA is running a follow-up to their very successful retail event late last year. Called &amp;#8220;8 More Ways to Sell Even More Stuff&amp;#8220;, it&amp;#8217;s all about selling online and multi-channel.
The focus this time is &amp;#8220;Content and Analysis&amp;#8221; and therefore it&amp;#8217;s no surprise that LouderVoice will be there talking about Social Commerce and how you can power that with Social-enabled Customer Reviews. No serious online business can ignore what their customers are saying about them and we&amp;#8217;ll show just how easy it is to benefit from those conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think LouderVoice should win a Europa Award?</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/10/27/think-loudervoice-should-win-a-europa-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 15:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/10/27/think-loudervoice-should-win-a-europa-award/</guid>
      <description>The Europas, the TechCrunch Europe Awards for European tech companies, will be held on November 19 in London. Entrants will be voted on by the industry and these results will guide a subsequent voting round from The Europas Advisory Board of experts.
 LouderVoice is listed in the &amp;#8220;Best Business or Enterprise Startup 2010&amp;#8221; Category. If you think we deserve the award, why not head over to the site and cast your vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Wins a Golden Spider</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/22/loudervoice-wins-a-golden-spider/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 19:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/22/loudervoice-wins-a-golden-spider/</guid>
      <description>We were terribly disappointed last Thursday that massive flooding in West Cork prevented us from attending the 2009 Golden Spiders Awards. The awards are the most high profile in Ireland and a win can have serious business benefits locally.
So imagine our shock to hear that we won the e-business category! We were up against some incredibly impressive competition. Getting this recognition from our industry peers on the judging panel really is satisfying.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>