<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trust on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/trust/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trust on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2020, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 15:33:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/trust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating Trust Thousands of Miles Away in Cairo with LouderVoice Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/11/28/2012-11-28-generating-trust-thousands-of-miles-away-in-cairo-with-loudervoice-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 15:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/11/28/2012-11-28-generating-trust-thousands-of-miles-away-in-cairo-with-loudervoice-reviews/</guid>
      <description>The first thing I do when I land on a site I haven&amp;#8217;t used before is to check their reviews. Good or bad, I want to see that it is a company which values feedback and is actively providing services or products.
We were really excited recently to sign-up Floradoor in Cairo as our first African client. This high-end florist delivers flowers locally for a global customer base and it has been a joy to read their reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Word of Mouth Still Most Trusted Resource Says Nielsen</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/04/16/word-of-mouth-still-most-trusted-resource-says-nielsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 09:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/04/16/word-of-mouth-still-most-trusted-resource-says-nielsen/</guid>
      <description>Nielsen’s latest Global Trust in Advertising report, which surveyed more than 28,000 Internet respondents in 56 countries, shows that 92% of people trust recommendations from friends and family, followed closely by 70% trusting online reviews.
Here are the highlight stats. Read the great piece about it over on Social Commerce Today.

We&amp;#8217;ve been in the reviews business for quite a few years so we&amp;#8217;re not remotely surprised by this data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>