<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Putplace on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/putplace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Putplace on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2017, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 19:01:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/putplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice nominated in The Europas</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/06/24/loudervoice-nominated-in-the-europas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/06/24/loudervoice-nominated-in-the-europas/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;re absolutely delighted to be nominated in the inaugural Europa Awards in the category of Best Web Application or Service (EMEA). The Europas are the Techcrunch Europe technology innovation awards for European tech companies and the ceremony will be held on July 9 in London. Public voting is now open in all categories.
 Major congratulations also go to Joe Drumgoole of Putplace who is nominated in the Best Startup Founder(s) (EMEA) category (Vote here) and Decisions for Heroes which is nominated in the Best Social Innovation (which benefits society, EMEA) category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice on The Right Hook</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2008/09/08/loudervoice-on-the-right-hook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 15:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2008/09/08/loudervoice-on-the-right-hook/</guid>
      <description>Conor is on The Right Hook radio show this evening on Newstalk with Joe Drumgoole from PutPlace. He&amp;#8217;ll be talking about the LouderVoice service in general and kicking off an SMS reviews push in conjunction with the show. You can listen live on the web here.
As part of this, we are launching our Simple SMS Review service. There&amp;#8217;ll be more detail in the next post but the key point is that unlike the existing service, no structure is required on your reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>