<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review-Enable on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://loudervoice.com/tags/review-enable/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review-Enable on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 14:55:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://loudervoice.com/tags/review-enable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice in 2008</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/01/04/loudervoice-in-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/01/04/loudervoice-in-2008/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve had a fantastic year in &lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/&#34;&gt;LouderVoice&lt;/a&gt; and it looks like 2009 is going to be even better with a raft of new releases in the next few months. Looking back over last year we achieved the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In January we launched &lt;a href=&#34;http://business.loudervoice.com/2008/01/29/easy-blog-reviews-with-flag-tags/&#34;&gt;Flag Tag reviewing&lt;/a&gt; which enabled any blogger to have their blog reviews collected by LouderVoice with two simple tags on a post.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We also added Twitter/SMS/Jaiku hashtag support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In February we sponsored the Best Blog Post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.awards.ie/&#34;&gt;Irish Blog Awards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In March we did our first major revamp with LouderVoice V2 adding on-site reviews and a ton of other features.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We also launched V2 of our WordPress Plugin. (Updated Plugin for WP 2.7 coming very soon!)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We spent from April to October busy fixing bugs and building our B2B offering&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In July we started using &lt;a href=&#34;http://getsatisfaction.com/loudervoice&#34;&gt;Get Satisfaction&lt;/a&gt; for Customer support. Don’t hesitate to add bug reports or feature requests there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In September we launched &lt;a href=&#34;http://business.loudervoice.com/2008/09/14/announcing-simple-sms-reviews/&#34;&gt;Simple SMS reviews&lt;/a&gt; requiring just a single keyword&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We were also Shortlisted in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.awards.ie/&#34;&gt;Irish Web Awards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In October we launched &lt;a href=&#34;http://business.loudervoice.com/&#34;&gt;LouderVoice for Business&lt;/a&gt; to great attention&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We were also &lt;a href=&#34;http://business.loudervoice.com/2008/10/15/loudervoice-nominated-for-new-company-of-the-year/&#34;&gt;shortlisted in the Irish Software Association Awards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And we kicked off our BES 2008 Offering for Irish Investors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In November, our first B2B client, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.klipsch.co.uk/&#34;&gt;Klipsch&lt;/a&gt;, went live&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In December we successfully closed a BES investment round which will ensure our continued success through 2009&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
