<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Awards on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/awards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Awards on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2020, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 15:55:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/awards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Think LouderVoice should win a Europa Award?</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2010/10/27/think-loudervoice-should-win-a-europa-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 15:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2010/10/27/think-loudervoice-should-win-a-europa-award/</guid>
      <description>The Europas, the TechCrunch Europe Awards for European tech companies, will be held on November 19 in London. Entrants will be voted on by the industry and these results will guide a subsequent voting round from The Europas Advisory Board of experts.
 LouderVoice is listed in the &amp;#8220;Best Business or Enterprise Startup 2010&amp;#8221; Category. If you think we deserve the award, why not head over to the site and cast your vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Wins a Golden Spider</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/22/loudervoice-wins-a-golden-spider/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 19:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/22/loudervoice-wins-a-golden-spider/</guid>
      <description>We were terribly disappointed last Thursday that massive flooding in West Cork prevented us from attending the 2009 Golden Spiders Awards. The awards are the most high profile in Ireland and a win can have serious business benefits locally.
So imagine our shock to hear that we won the e-business category! We were up against some incredibly impressive competition. Getting this recognition from our industry peers on the judging panel really is satisfying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mashable Open Web Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2008/11/12/mashable-open-web-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 23:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2008/11/12/mashable-open-web-awards/</guid>
      <description>If you like what we are doing on LouderVoice, why not vote for us in the Mashable Open Web Awards? You can do it below.
 Mashable Open Web Awards  Don&amp;#8217;t forget to vote for all your favourite Irish WebApps, many of which can be found over at Web2Ireland.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Nominated for New Company of The Year</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2008/10/15/loudervoice-nominated-for-new-company-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 14:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2008/10/15/loudervoice-nominated-for-new-company-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>What a fantastic couple of weeks in the life of LouderVoice. Yesterday we found out we&amp;#8217;ve been shortlisted for New Company of The Year by The Irish Software Association. This is one helluva heavy-duty event and we&amp;#8217;re nervous about the interview process already.

There will be lots more announcements and coverage in the next two weeks so watch closely.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>