<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ecommerce on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://loudervoice.com/tags/ecommerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ecommerce on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2024, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 15:56:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://loudervoice.com/tags/ecommerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio of Conor’s Talk at IIA Retail Event</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2011/03/15/audio-of-conors-talk-at-iia-retail-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 15:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2011/03/15/audio-of-conors-talk-at-iia-retail-event/</guid>
      <description>My talk on customer reviews at the IIA&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;8 More Ways to Sell Even More Stuff&amp;#8221; event seemed to go down very well.
Judge for yourself. Hopefully you&amp;#8217;ll find it useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great e-commerce stats round up from Econsultancy</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/11/08/great-e-commerce-stats-round-up-from-econsultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 07:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/11/08/great-e-commerce-stats-round-up-from-econsultancy/</guid>
      <description>Lots of very interesting headline stats about e-commerce over on the Econsultancy site. It appears that the prediction of the first online Christmas (50p in the £) by 2015 is well on its way to coming true.
 IMRG predicts that £6.4bn will be spent online in December 2010, up from £5.5bn last year. Total online spending for 2010 is predicted to reach £57,8bn, compared with £49.8bn in 2009.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Reviews on your site in 5 minutes?</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/07/customer-reviews-on-your-site-in-5-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/07/customer-reviews-on-your-site-in-5-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Yes you can! Renowned SEO expert Richard Hearne of Red Cardinal did exactly that this afternoon with the LouderVoice EasyReview system.

Think you can beat him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Brothers goes live with the new LouderVoice Reviews Widget</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/04/28/bubble-brothers-goes-live-with-the-new-loudervoice-reviews-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/04/28/bubble-brothers-goes-live-with-the-new-loudervoice-reviews-widget/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;re pleased as punch to announce that our brand new customer reviews widget has just gone live on the Bubble Brothers wine site. Julian, their Wine 2.0 guru, has always been at the forefront of social media adoption and the addition of our widget complements all of their other online activities beautifully.

The key thing about the widget is the ease of implementation. One line of code was added to the Bubble Brothers product page template (they use Ecommerce Templates for their site), a few minor logo tweaks later and they were up and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet shoppers rate recommendations and user reviews over price</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/04/08/internet-shoppers-rate-personal-recommendations-and-user-reviews-over-price/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 16:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/04/08/internet-shoppers-rate-personal-recommendations-and-user-reviews-over-price/</guid>
      <description>The LouderVoice customer reviews service is getting a lot of attention from businesses who are looking for ways to retain customers and grow sales in these difficult times.
So the latest research from Avail Intellingence comes as no surprise to us. InternetRetailing reports that the research shows over a third (36%) of respondents rated peer opinions such as recommendations, reviews and customer generated wish lists as the most useful aspect of an Internet-shopping site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>