<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sms on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://loudervoice.com/tags/sms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sms on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2024, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:01:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://loudervoice.com/tags/sms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews on Facebook Pages</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/08/27/loudervoice-reviews-on-facebook-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/08/27/loudervoice-reviews-on-facebook-pages/</guid>
      <description>We have just added a new Facebook capability for all of our customers. They can now show all their latest reviews in a dedicated &amp;#8220;Our Reviews&amp;#8221; tab on their Facebook Page. Whilst our Facebook Connect implementation has always given reviewers the ability to post their reviews to their personal wall, this new feature enables our clients to showcase their reviews from all their products and services in one place.
Now a simple review written on a client&amp;#8217;s site or submitted by SMS can appear on their Facebook Page within minutes, building confidence and guiding others who want to know more about that business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Simple SMS Reviews</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/09/14/announcing-simple-sms-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2008 18:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/09/14/announcing-simple-sms-reviews/</guid>
      <description>We kicked off SMS reviewing last year using the same structured message format which we devised for Twitter and Jaiku. Whilst it suits a lot of our users, particularly those who want their reviews to appear instantly, many others felt that the structure was overly complex.
Based on this user feedback, we are now launching Simple SMS Reviews. The idea here is that you send your review to the same number as before (+353-87-9409325 or +44-778-6205133), you begin your SMS with the keyword &amp;#8220;Re&amp;#8221; and then the remainder of the SMS is your review in whatever style you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a Gift Hamper for Taste of Cork Reviews</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/06/24/win-a-gift-hamper-for-taste-of-cork-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 11:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/06/24/win-a-gift-hamper-for-taste-of-cork-reviews/</guid>
      <description>The Taste of Cork Food Festival is coming this weekend in the deep south of Ireland. There will by myriad stands offering food and beverages to sample including lots of famous Munster Artisan producers.
We&amp;#8217;re partnering with several of the exhibitors including Ummera and Bubble Brothers to encourage those who attend to review both the event and the individual stands. Reviews can be submitted by any of the usual methods but SMS seems the most appropriate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chips in Tipp</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/02/27/chips-in-tipp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 10:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/02/27/chips-in-tipp/</guid>
      <description>Bernie Goldbach, well known blogger/journalist/lecturer/consultant got some teenagers to recommend chippers in Tipperary by SMS. We now have 7 of the top Chips in Tipp on LouderVoice. What&amp;#8217;s your favourite?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>