<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://loudervoice.com/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2024, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 00:30:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://loudervoice.com/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice and Ireland in French Business Magazine Stratégies</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2011/12/28/loudervoice-and-ireland-in-french-business-magazine-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 00:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2011/12/28/loudervoice-and-ireland-in-french-business-magazine-strategies/</guid>
      <description>I had the pleasure of being interviewed recently for the leading French Business Magazine, Stratégies. It was about doing business in Ireland and some of the positive aspects of setting up here despite the recession.
You&amp;#8217;ll need pretty fluent French to read the entire article but there are some good nuggets in there.
Enjoy!
Strategies Ireland LouderVoice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think LouderVoice should win a Europa Award?</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/10/27/think-loudervoice-should-win-a-europa-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 15:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/10/27/think-loudervoice-should-win-a-europa-award/</guid>
      <description>The Europas, the TechCrunch Europe Awards for European tech companies, will be held on November 19 in London. Entrants will be voted on by the industry and these results will guide a subsequent voting round from The Europas Advisory Board of experts.
 LouderVoice is listed in the &amp;#8220;Best Business or Enterprise Startup 2010&amp;#8221; Category. If you think we deserve the award, why not head over to the site and cast your vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>58% of E-retailers Say Primary ROI is in Listening to Customers</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/10/08/34-of-e-retailers-say-social-marketing-increases-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 16:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/10/08/34-of-e-retailers-say-social-marketing-increases-sales/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;re always happy to see statistics to back up what we already know and tell clients every day:
The report, which was conducted by Forrester Research Inc. on behalf of Shop.org, the online retailing division of the National Retail Federation, an industry trade group, notes that most retailers regard customer ratings and reviews as useful and directly correlated to sales.
You can read more about this research at Internet Retailer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wondering what reviews can do for your business?</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/03/19/wondering-what-reviews-can-do-for-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 13:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/03/19/wondering-what-reviews-can-do-for-your-business/</guid>
      <description>How about adding $2.7B to you bottom line?
Via Econsultancy:
 &amp;#8230; calculates that, since displaying the most helpful reviews has increased sales in the media products category by 20%, overall this feature was worth $2.7bn to Amazon
 Contact business@loudervoice.com if you&amp;#8217;d like to hear how reviews can help your business!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>