<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Loudervoice For Business on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/loudervoice-for-business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Loudervoice For Business on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2017, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 23:03:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/loudervoice-for-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Puddleducks Customers Get a Louder Voice</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/04/14/puddleducks-customers-get-a-louder-voice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 23:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/04/14/puddleducks-customers-get-a-louder-voice/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s always a delight to work with like-minded companies so we were doubly pleased when Puddleducks.ie contacted us recently about using the LouderVoice customer reviews system on their site.
 Puddleducks is a rapidly growing online retailer of outdoor clothing for both children’s and adults. In fact,  we first encountered them as personal customers of their fantastic products. Their range includes Swedish designed dungarees, jackets and trousers for children, as well as waterproof clothing and work wear for adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice in 2008</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/01/04/loudervoice-in-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/01/04/loudervoice-in-2008/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;ve had a fantastic year in LouderVoice and it looks like 2009 is going to be even better with a raft of new releases in the next few months. Looking back over last year we achieved the following:
 In January we launched Flag Tag reviewing which enabled any blogger to have their blog reviews collected by LouderVoice with two simple tags on a post. We also added Twitter/SMS/Jaiku hashtag support In February we sponsored the Best Blog Post in the Irish Blog Awards In March we did our first major revamp with LouderVoice V2 adding on-site reviews and a ton of other features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice for Business launched</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2008/10/06/loudervoice-for-business-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 22:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2008/10/06/loudervoice-for-business-launched/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few months we have been trialling our business services with several clients. Some of those are already live, others will go live over the next quarter. We now have a very nice brochure site to go with these services and a very powerful content moderation back-end for our clients.
The LouderVoice for Business site gives the high level overview of our services which are currently in three areas:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>