<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Facebook Connect on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/facebook-connect/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Facebook Connect on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2017, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:01:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/facebook-connect/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews on Facebook Pages</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2010/08/27/loudervoice-reviews-on-facebook-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2010/08/27/loudervoice-reviews-on-facebook-pages/</guid>
      <description>We have just added a new Facebook capability for all of our customers. They can now show all their latest reviews in a dedicated &amp;#8220;Our Reviews&amp;#8221; tab on their Facebook Page. Whilst our Facebook Connect implementation has always given reviewers the ability to post their reviews to their personal wall, this new feature enables our clients to showcase their reviews from all their products and services in one place.
Now a simple review written on a client&amp;#8217;s site or submitted by SMS can appear on their Facebook Page within minutes, building confidence and guiding others who want to know more about that business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice at Facebook Garage Ireland 2</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/07/04/loudervoice-at-facebook-garage-ireland-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 08:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/2009/07/04/loudervoice-at-facebook-garage-ireland-2/</guid>
      <description>We had a fantastic time at the second Irish Facebook Garage in Dublin on Thursday. A packed room of approx 150 people with a wide range of backgrounds heard 5 speakers cover a variety of topics over the space of 2.5 hours.
There will be full coverage including video and all the PPTs available over on Web2Ireland at some point next week. In the meantime, here are some screenshots of Conor&amp;#8217;s live demo of the LouderVoice reviews widget + Facebook Connect in action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>