<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seo on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/seo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seo on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2006 - 2023, Argolon Solutions Ltd; all rights reserved. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 18:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.loudervoice.com/tags/seo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews SEO Add-On for ASP.NET just released</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/05/10/loudervoice-reviews-seo-add-on-for-asp-net-just-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 18:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2012/05/10/loudervoice-reviews-seo-add-on-for-asp-net-just-released/</guid>
      <description>One of the most common requests we get from partners and customers is to have the same reviews SEO functionality on ASP.NET as they do for PHP and WordPress sites. And we&amp;#8217;re delighted to say that this is now available.
All of our Packages provide Google Juice and Star Ratings in Search results to client sites via our review Hub, LouderYou. The advantage of this approach is ease of deployment. Our code can be added in seconds to a web-page and reviews are then live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Exhibiting at The Hotel Website Marketing Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2010/09/10/loudervoice-exhibiting-at-the-hotel-website-marketing-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2010/09/10/loudervoice-exhibiting-at-the-hotel-website-marketing-conference/</guid>
      <description>Last year&amp;#8217;s Hotel Website Marketing Conference was a superb event. I spoke on the value of customer reviews but I learned 10x that from the other speakers on all of the online marketing (and other) challenges/opportunities being faced by hotels.
 Ciarán and the team have outdone themselves this year with the speaker line-up. As we just couldn&amp;#8217;t miss it, we&amp;#8217;ve decided to exhibit there too. Keep an eye out for the LouderVoice stand and pop over for a chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Reviews on your site in 5 minutes?</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/07/customer-reviews-on-your-site-in-5-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/11/07/customer-reviews-on-your-site-in-5-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Yes you can! Renowned SEO expert Richard Hearne of Red Cardinal did exactly that this afternoon with the LouderVoice EasyReview system.

Think you can beat him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citylocal Cork Reviews on LouderVoice</title>
      <link>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/09/10/citylocal-cork-reviews-on-loudervoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 10:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.loudervoice.com/blog/2009/09/10/citylocal-cork-reviews-on-loudervoice/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;ve always been impressed with the Citylocal franchise which was built by Nazir Daud in the UK. Paul Brugger launched the Cork site last year and it has been growing at an amazing rate. CityLocal Cork is a Business Directory and community website that provides local information on Businesses, News, Events, Free Ads, Property and Cinema listings.
 Visitors to Citylocal often leave reviews of the businesses they find there. We are now aggregating those reviews into our system, adding to the already powerful SEO mojo of Citylocal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>