<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hreview on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</title>
    <link>https://loudervoice.com/tags/hreview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hreview on LouderVoice Customer Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 11:48:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://loudervoice.com/tags/hreview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice SEO Add-On Now Available for Expression Engine</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/08/22/loudervoice-seo-add-on-now-available-for-expression-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 11:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/08/22/loudervoice-seo-add-on-now-available-for-expression-engine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many of our clients on PHP platforms like WordPress, Joomla, Drupal have long benefited from our SEO Add-On.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of our Packages provide Google Juice and Star Ratings in Search results to client sites via our review Hub, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.louderyou.com/&#34;&gt;LouderYou&lt;/a&gt;. The advantage of this approach is ease of deployment. Our code can be added in seconds to a web-page and reviews are then live. Those reviews are indexed on our hub within hours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews Plugin for WordPress now available</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/03/02/loudervoice-reviews-plugin-for-wordpress-now-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 16:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2012/03/02/loudervoice-reviews-plugin-for-wordpress-now-available/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;More and more sites are moving to &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org&#34;&gt;WordPress&lt;/a&gt; as their platform. We have long been WP users and all of our sites are built on it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The LouderVoice reviews system has always supported WordPress sites but we recently decided to make it even easier to deploy on them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/02/loudervoice-reviews-plugin-for-wordpress-now-available/blue-l.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-full wp-image-2676 aligncenter&#34; title=&#34;blue-l&#34; src=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/02/loudervoice-reviews-plugin-for-wordpress-now-available/blue-l.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;150&#34; height=&#34;150&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new LouderVoice Reviews plug-in is now available and included in the price of all of our Packages. With a few quick clicks, you can install the plug-in and configure reviews for one or more pages on any WP site.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fastnet Line Cork-Swansea Ferry on-board with LouderVoice</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/08/06/fastnet-line-cork-swansea-ferry-on-board-with-loudervoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 14:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2010/08/06/fastnet-line-cork-swansea-ferry-on-board-with-loudervoice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Business books will be written about the amazing story of the new Fastnet Line &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fastnetline.com/&#34;&gt;Ferry to Ireland&lt;/a&gt;. This much needed service operating from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fastnetline.com/&#34;&gt;Swansea to Cork&lt;/a&gt; is proving to be a major success for the region. So you can imagine our excitement at LouderVoice becoming part of this story by powering the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fastnetline.com/ireland_ferry_reviews.html&#34;&gt;customer reviews on their site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fastnetline.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-full wp-image-1743  aligncenter&#34; title=&#34;Fastnet Line&#34; src=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/08/06/fastnet-line-cork-swansea-ferry-on-board-with-loudervoice/logo2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;266&#34; height=&#34;55&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whilst reviews are important for any business, their importance to new businesses cannot be under-estimated. The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fastnetline.com/ireland_ferry_reviews.html&#34;&gt;response from travellers&lt;/a&gt; has been phenomenal since reviews were turned on last week. The unique direct feedback has enabled Fastnet Line to immediately discover what is working very well and what can potentially be changed or improved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Simple Mini-Reviews on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/06/24/ultra-simple-mini-reviews-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 18:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/06/24/ultra-simple-mini-reviews-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/&#34;&gt;LouderVoice&lt;/a&gt; was the first reviews company to realise the importance of &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/loudervoice&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;. That’s why we’re the people behind &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/review&#34;&gt;@review&lt;/a&gt; which we launched in June 2007.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since then we’ve played and tweaked mini-reviews based on user feedback.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Following more research we realised that many people were doing mini-reviews using the simple method of just adding #review on to the end of the tweet. This was also the preferred approach in our recent poll.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice Reviews for Google Android</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/05/23/loudervoice-reviews-for-google-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/05/23/loudervoice-reviews-for-google-android/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday evening we uploaded the first public beta of our Google Android mobile application to the Android Market.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter size-full wp-image-218&#34; title=&#34;lv_android_01&#34; src=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/05/lv_android_01.png&#34; alt=&#34;lv_android_01&#34; width=&#34;320&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the first Irish Android application and one of the very first reviewing applications on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You’ll have to patiently wait for the launches of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.htc.com/www/product/magic/overview.html&#34;&gt;HTC Magic&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://gizmodo.com/5229244/meet-the-i7500-samsungs-first-android-phone&#34;&gt;Samsung I7500&lt;/a&gt; before Â most Irish people can try it out. Anyone living in countries where Android is already live can install it now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updated LouderVoice WordPress Plugin</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/02/01/updated-loudervoice-wordpress-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 15:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/02/01/updated-loudervoice-wordpress-plugin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have two bits of news about our LouderVoice plug-in. The first is that it is now WordPress 2.7 compatible and the second is that we have moved the hosting over to &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/loudervoice/&#34;&gt;WordPress.org&lt;/a&gt;. This means that from now on, when we update it, you’ll see a notification in your WordPress Admin Panel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apart from the 2.7 compatibility change, the only other major feature is that you can opt to have all the contextual information about the review, including the stars, at the end of the text. Full instructions in the readme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Opinion on Free-Form Twitter Reviews</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/01/24/your-opinion-on-free-form-twitter-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 14:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2009/01/24/your-opinion-on-free-form-twitter-reviews/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As you probably know, LouderVoice was the first company to identify Twitter as an important source of reviews. We launched LouderTweets structured reviews all the way back in June 2007. We are also the people behind the @review user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whilst many people have used the structured reviews since then, many others have found the structure difficult to remember or just plain awkward.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We turned on free-form reviews on SMS last year and most people are much happier with that. They simply send an SMS to us beginning with “RE” (or one of our partners’ keywords) and the remainder of the review is in whatever style they like.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New version of LouderVoice WordPress Plug-in</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/06/04/new-version-of-loudervoice-wordpress-plug-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 07:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/06/04/new-version-of-loudervoice-wordpress-plug-in/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many thanks to Loud Reviewer &lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/people/frankp/&#34;&gt;Frank Prendergast&lt;/a&gt; for spotting a bug in our WordPress plug-in. This bug prevented users from setting review posts to publish in the future. The bug has now been fixed and the updated plug-in is &lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/wordpress_plugin&#34;&gt;available here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You’ve probably noticed how quiet we’ve been on the blog. Not only have we been fixing a lot of small bugs on the site that crept in with the Version2 launch but we’re been working hard on building our API. This will enable other sites to embed our reviewing functionality on their pages. We’ll be going live very shortly with the first partner on this. This XML API is accessible directly, using a PHP library or using a JS library (with more coming soon).Ã‚Â  If this is something you’d like to hear more about, please contact conor AT loudervoice DOT com. We’re putting together some information pages on it at the moment too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LouderVoice WordPress Plug-in Version 2</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/03/30/loudervoice-wordpress-plug-in-version-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 13:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/03/30/loudervoice-wordpress-plug-in-version-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve been promising it forever and now we’re finally ready to unveil the all-new LouderVoice WordPress plug-in V2.0. This enables you to write reviews on your blog using an open standard called hReview. Sites like LouderVoice can then index and interpret them more intelligently than raw blog-posts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new plug-in is a total re-write based on lots of user feedback and, in particular, some fantastic suggestions and guidance from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bytesurgery.com/blog/&#34;&gt;Robin Blandford&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Blog Reviews with Flag Tags</title>
      <link>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/01/29/easy-blog-reviews-with-flag-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 01:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://loudervoice.com/blog/2008/01/29/easy-blog-reviews-with-flag-tags/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The approach we have taken with reviews on blogs until now has been built around a standard called hreview. Many bloggers are a fan of this portable format and we continue to support it strongly. But we have received many requests for something more lightweight which still enables people to get their reviews into &lt;a href=&#34;https://loudervoice.com/&#34;&gt;LouderVoice&lt;/a&gt; but takes much less effort.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After trying a variety of approaches we have settled on something we are calling Flag Tags (thanks to &lt;a href=&#34;http://bifsniff.com/&#34;&gt;Frank Prendergast&lt;/a&gt; for coining this). The idea is simple. If you are writing a blog post that is a review, you need to ensure three very basic things:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
